const stuff = [
  { question: "1 - 1", answer: "0" },
  { question: "2 - 1", answer: "1" },
  { question: "3 - 1", answer: "2" },
  { question: "4 - 1", answer: "3" },
  { question: "5 - 1", answer: "4" },
  { question: "6 - 1", answer: "5" },
  { question: "7 - 1", answer: "6" },
  { question: "8 - 1", answer: "7" },
  { question: "9 - 1", answer: "8" },
  { question: "10 - 1", answer: "9" },
  { question: "2 - 2", answer: "0" },
  { question: "3 - 2", answer: "1" },
  { question: "4 - 2", answer: "2" },
  { question: "5 - 2", answer: "3" },
  { question: "6 - 2", answer: "4" },
  { question: "7 - 2", answer: "5" },
  { question: "8 - 2", answer: "6" },
  { question: "9 - 2", answer: "7" },
  { question: "10 - 2", answer: "8" },
  { question: "3 - 3", answer: "0" },
  { question: "4 - 3", answer: "1" },
  { question: "5 - 3", answer: "2" },
  { question: "6 - 3", answer: "3" },
  { question: "7 - 3", answer: "4" },
  { question: "8 - 3", answer: "5" },
  { question: "9 - 3", answer: "6" },
  { question: "10 - 3", answer: "7" },
  { question: "4 - 4", answer: "0" },
  { question: "5 - 4", answer: "1" },
  { question: "6 - 4", answer: "2" },
  { question: "7 - 4", answer: "3" },
  { question: "8 - 4", answer: "4" },
  { question: "9 - 4", answer: "5" },
  { question: "10 - 4", answer: "6" },
  { question: "5 - 5", answer: "0" },
  { question: "6 - 5", answer: "1" },
  { question: "7 - 5", answer: "2" },
  { question: "8 - 5", answer: "3" },
  { question: "9 - 5", answer: "4" },
  { question: "10 - 5", answer: "5" },
  { question: "6 - 6", answer: "0" },
  { question: "7 - 6", answer: "1" },
  { question: "8 - 6", answer: "2" },
  { question: "9 - 6", answer: "3" },
  { question: "10 - 6", answer: "4" },
  { question: "7 - 7", answer: "0" },
  { question: "8 - 7", answer: "1" },
  { question: "9 - 7", answer: "2" },
  { question: "10 - 7", answer: "3" },
  { question: "8 - 8", answer: "0" },
  { question: "9 - 8", answer: "1" },
  { question: "10 - 8", answer: "2" },
  { question: "9 - 9", answer: "0" },
  { question: "10 - 9", answer: "1" },
  { question: "10 - 10", answer: "0" },
];

export default stuff;
